We all know fresh is best when it comes to food.
我们都知道，说到食物，新鲜的最好。
However, most produce at the store goes through weeks of travel and covers hundreds of miles before reaching the table.
然而，商店里的大多数农产品在端上餐桌之前，都要经过数周的运输，行程数百英里。
While farmers’ markets are a solid choice to reduce the journey, Babylon Micro-Farm (BMF) shortens it even more.
虽然农贸市场是缩短这段路程的可靠选择，但巴比伦微型农场（BMF）能把这段路程缩得更短。
BMF is an indoor garden system.
BMF是一种室内种植系统。
It can be set up for a family.
它可以安装在家里，供一家人使用。
Additionally, it could serve a larger audience such as a hospital, restaurant or school.
此外，它也可以服务于更大的群体，比如医院、餐馆或学校。
The innovative design requires little effort to achieve a reliable weekly supply of fresh greens.
这种创新设计只需花很少的力气，就能实现每周稳定供应新鲜绿叶蔬菜。
Specifically, it’s a farm that relies on new technology.
具体来说，它是一个依靠新技术的农场。
Connected through the Cloud, BMF is remotely monitored.
BMF通过云端联网，接受远程监控。
Also, there is a convenient app that provides growing data in real time.
此外，还有一个便捷的应用程序，可以实时提供种植数据。
Because the system is automated, it significantly reduces the amount of water needed to grow plants.
由于该系统是自动化的，因此大大减少了种植植物所需的水量。
Rather than watering rows of soil, the system provides just the right amount to each plant.
该系统不是一垄一垄地给土壤浇水，而是给每株植物提供恰好适量的水。
After harvest, users simply replace the plants with a new pre-seeded pod to get the next growth cycle started.
收获之后，用户只需用一个新的预播种容器替换掉原来的植物，就能开始下一个生长周期。
Moreover, having a system in the same building where the food is eaten means zero emissions from transporting plants from soil to salad.
而且，把系统设在人们食用这些食物的同一栋建筑里，意味着植物从土壤到沙拉的运输过程实现零排放。
In addition, there’s no need for pesticides and other chemicals that pollute traditional farms and the surrounding environment.
此外，它也不需要使用会污染传统农场及其周边环境的杀虫剂和其他化学品。
BMF employees live out sustainability in their everyday lives.
BMF的员工在日常生活中践行可持续理念。
About half of them walk or bike to work.
其中大约一半人步行或骑自行车上班。
Inside the office, they encourage recycling and waste reduction by limiting garbage cans and avoiding single-use plastic.
在办公室里，他们通过限制垃圾桶数量和避免使用一次性塑料制品，来提倡回收利用、减少废物。
“We are passionate about reducing waste, carbon and chemicals in our environment,” said a BMF employee.
“我们热衷于减少环境中的废物、碳和化学物质，”一位BMF员工说。